十二 四 十一号桌上菜
Pick up! Tables 12, 4, 11.
来了
Got it.
等你丫有空...
Hey, when you get a second,
麻烦把淫眼从我奶上移开
stop looking at my boobs.
麻烦一下
Excuse me.
服务生
Waitress?
小二
Dude?
您好 请问要点什么
Hi, what can I get ya?
我们要...
We need some...
看了会不爽吗
Is that annoying?
觉得对方又欠扁又无礼吗
Is that obnoxious and rude?
你工作时有人这么弄你
Would you find it distracting if someone did that to you
你会觉得烦吗
while you were working?
哎呀 忘记你没工作了 抱歉
Oh, you don't have a job. Sorry.
靠 伙计 她完胜呀
Damn, dude, she burned you.
别搞错了 小痞子
No, hipster.
别以为我跟你是一国的
Do not think we're on the same team.
咱俩到死都不是同路人
We have nothing in common.
姐戴帽子挡酷寒
I wear knit hats when it's cold out.
二货戴帽学酷玩[乐队]
You wear knit hats cause of Coldplay.
你的纹身是想气死你爹
You have tattoos to piss off your dad.
我爹压根不知他是我爹
My dad doesn't know he's my dad.
最后
And finally,
你觉得
you think...
一声穿云指 我千军万马来服务
this is the sound that gets you service.
要我说
I think...
一声穿云指 我如瀑下阴也干枯
This is the sound that dries up my vagina.
那位俄国服务生呢 怎么不见了
The other waitress disappeared, the Russian one.
我们想要山葵酱
We need horseradish.
拜托您了
Please.
妹妹真乖 这样才有礼貌嘛
That, ladies, is how you treat a waitress.
宝莲娜
Paulina!
爽 爽死了
Oh, so... so good, oh...
抱歉 不知道你在休息
Oh, sorry, I didn't realize you were on break.
我要山葵酱
I just need some horseradish.
-给 -收到
- Here. - Oh, cool.
请问 服务生去哪了
Excuse me, where's my waitress?
她马上来[高潮]
She's coming.
厄尔
Earl.
Earl!
我做了你最爱的红丝绒蛋糕
I made your favorite, red velvet.
我的蛋蛋妹给我带来了小蛋糕
My little cupcake brought me a cupcake.
我还是把钱给你吧
Let me pay you for that.
不用 我请客
Oh, no, no. It's on the house.
你生日嘛
It's your birthday.
过完生日要几岁了啊
How old are you gonna be?
厄尔 你要小个三岁 咱俩就成了
Oh, Earl, if you were just three years younger.
麦克斯 麦克斯 大新闻
Max, Max, big news.
新老板炒了俄国妞宝莲娜
The new boss fired that Russian waitress, Paulina.
大胸金丝猫被发现其实是个死间谍
Turns out chesty Kournikova was Vladimir Puttin' it out.
早安 我带了你的工资来
Hello today. I have paycheck for you.
我有话问你 你炒了宝莲娜吗 阿憨
I need to talk to you. You fired Paulina, Han?
我已经不叫李憨了
I am no longer Han Lee.
我取了新的英文名字
I have new American name
好适应新时代"得"社会
to go with changing neighborhood.
是新时代"的"社会
To go with the changing neighborhood.
移民考试的时候别又说错了
You need to remember this for your immigration exam.
行 好适应新时代"的"社会
Correct. To go with the changing neighborhood.
小笼
Bryce?
你改名叫李小笼啊
Your name is Bryce Lee?
等等 等一下
Wait, wait, um, um, um...
别再招新人来了 好吗
Don't hire a new waitress, okay?
反正活儿总是我全包
I've been doing all the work anyway,
让我多拿一份工资 补贴家计吧
and I really could use the extra money.
你需要帮手
You need help.
-不用 -谁都需要帮手
- No, I don't. - Everyone need help sometimes.
我不用 我当了一辈子的侍应
I don't. I've been waiting my whole life, okay?
在餐厅 酒吧都做过侍应
I've waited on tables, I've waited in bars,
甚至在家等验孕结果
I've waited on home pregnancy tests.
我已经雇新人了
I already hire new waitress.
她以前在曼哈顿顶级餐厅工作过
She work in all top restaurants in Manhattan.
我都把宝莲娜的制服给她了
I gave her Paulina's uniform.
李先生 有点事情想问问
Mr. Lee, not to complain,
这件制服好像有人穿过了呢
but I think someone wore this uniform before me,
而且是刚刚才穿过
like right before me.
可不可以帮我换一件全新的呀
Is it possible that I could get another one?
换件没这么湿漉漉的
Maybe one that's a little less moist.
另外 我的肤色跟黄芥末色不太搭
Also this mustard color doesn't really go with my skin tone,
跟芥末渍也不搭
neither do the mustard stains...
跟这各式污渍 异味更是不搭
And these various other stains, and smells.
白白的是蛤蜊浓汤渍吧...
I hope that's clam chowder.
所以
So...
为了大家
I think it'd be better for everyone,
以及我的免疫系统着想
including my immune system,
我就穿自己这身就好了
if I just keep on wearing what I'm wearing,
那件就省了 我这身可是香奈儿
and not the apron,'cause this is chanel.
感谢聆听
So thank you,
本小姐要上岗啦
and let's waitress.
这娇娇女明显就是
Whatever that is,
来错地方打错工了
it does not belong in this diner.
她应该去演电视
It belongs in a show on Bravo.
她是金发妞 金发闪闪
But she blonde, hair so shiny,
有助财源广进啊
good for business.
你都去哪找到这些歪瓜裂枣的啊
Where do you even find these people?
俄罗斯妓女 再前一位还是吸毒妹
The Russian hooker, the one before that was a meth addict.
你去训练她 我可是老板
You train her, I am boss.
老板中的老板
Da boss.
好 那你先去命令她穿上制服
Fine, but make her wear the uniform.
真不能让吸毒的回来吗
Are you sure we can't get the meth addict back?
她是毁尸灭迹打扫神人呢
She was really good at cleaning.
可她吸毒到牙掉光了
But her teeth fall out.
你也太以貌取人了吧
You are really judgmental, you know that?
我就说一回 仔细听
I'm only gonna say this once, so pay attention.
我是卡洛琳 你叫麦克斯 对吗
I'm Caroline, by the way. And you're Max?
先别建立感情
Don't get attached.
这间威廉伯格餐厅 老板是李憨
This is the Williamsburg diner, owned by Han Lee,
最近刚改名叫李小笼
Who just changed his name to Bryce Lee,
他应该是患了不被当笑话会死的病
because I guess he wants people to take him even less seriously.
八个月前他向俄国黑帮顶下这餐厅
Eight months ago he bought it from the Russian mob.
以前客源通常是东欧小流氓 吸毒妓女
Clientele used to be all eastern bloc criminals and crack whores,
他顶过来之后 客源就跑光了
but then he took it over and ruined it.
哟 性感辣妹
Hey, sexy woman.
今儿个性感动人啊
You look so pretty today.
美得我差点忘了你是悍妇了
You look so beautiful, I forgot how bad your personality is.
承蒙夸奖 奥列格
Thanks, Oleg.
嗨 芭比小妞
Hey, Barbie.
他是奥列格
That's Oleg.
他将会不停地用烂招泡你
He will hit on you aggressively and relentlessly.
他的自信多到爆棚
He doesn't realize he looks like that,
可惜我没多余的善心点醒他
and I don't have the heart to tell him.
小姐 可以给份菜单吗
Miss, could we have some menus?
当然
Oh, sure.
不要微笑
Don't smile.
你拉高服务标准 我就得跟上
Cause it raises the bar, and then I have to smile,
那样太累人了
and I can't be doing that.
微笑又累人又有害健康
It's exhausting and I have a bad back.
那是我的恋人厄尔
That's Earl, we're in love.
别跟他多讲话
Do not talk to him,
除非你想显得更"白"痴
unless you want to feel whiter than you already are.
还有那块污渍
Oh, and that stain?
其实是男人"精"华
Not clam chowder.
去把番茄酱连一起
Go marry the ketchups.
"联姻"起 马上好
Marry the ketchups. I'm on it.
"联姻"完 弄离婚吧
Okay. Now divorce the ketchups.
停 停 停
Stop! Stop! Stop!
让番茄酱离婚纯属我鬼扯
There's no such thing as divorcing the ketchups.
你压根就没当过服务生对吧
You've never waitressed a day in your life.
我真的做过
Yes, I have.
看完你这出
You expect me to believe you
奇葩的演出后 鬼才信你
after watching that whole Temple Grandin routine?
-我去跟老板检举你 -别 求你了
- I'm telling Lee. - Okay, okay,
我的确稍微美化了我的简历
I may have enhanced my resume.
美化 你当参加巴黎时尚展啊
Enhanced? What, are we in Paris?
求你了 我真的很需要这份工
Please, I really need this job, okay?
我们家一无所有了
We lost all of our money.
我的信托基金被拿去支付律师费
My trust fund was taken for legal fees.
老爸又入狱了
My dad is in jail.
干嘛 难不成你是马丁·钱宁的女儿啊
What? What are you, Martin Channing's daughter?
报纸在哪
Where's the paper?
马丁·钱宁
Martin Channing?
骗光整座城的人是你老爸
The guy who ripped off the entire city is your father.
他只跟我们说今年生意挺好
He told us we were having a good year.
你是卡洛琳·钱宁
You're Caroline Channing.
你可是亿万富翁
You're like a billionaire.
曾是 曾是亿万富翁
Was. Was a billionaire.
所有资产都被冻结了 全没了
They froze all our assets, everything's gone.
我只能拿几样东西走
I only have what I could grab,
可我全拿了没用的东西
and I grabbed all the wrong things.
-你认识总统吧 -见过
- So do you know the president? - I've met him.
-他很性感吧 -他就是个总统
- He's hot. - He's the president.
-你去过瑞士吧 -去过
- Have you been to Switzerland? - Yes.
-你有马吗 -有
- Do you have a horse? - Yes.
-认识帕丽斯·希尔顿吗 -不认识 她太老了
- Do you know Paris Hilton? - No, she's a hundred.
麻烦一下 两杯热巧克力
Excuse me, uh, two hot chocolate, please.
马上好
Comin' up.
让我来吧
Let me do that, please.
我学东西可快了
I'm a really fast learner.
沃顿商学院毕业
I went to Wharton business school.
SAT考了两千三百分
I got 2,300 on my SAT.
那你做得出热巧克力吗
Can you make a hot chocolate, or not?
搞定
Nailed it.
小费均分 把你的拿来
We split the tips. Give me yours.
比我预计的好多了
You did better than I thought you would.
我刚想到了一个
Listen, tonight I thought of a way
赚外快的办法
we could make some extra money.
那些红丝绒蛋糕
They've totally underestimated the price
定价实在低的离谱
point on those red velvet cupcakes.
在曼哈顿这至少卖七块
In Manhattan the asking price is at least seven,
我们就卖七块 赚价差中饱私囊
so we could sell them for seven, and then pocket the difference.
难道你不觉得有什么不对吗
Nothing about that sounds wrong to you?
做蛋糕的傻子定价这么低
It's not our fault that the idiot who makes the cupcakes
又不是我们的错
doesn't know their worth.
我就是做蛋糕的那傻子
I'm the idiot who makes the cupcakes.
我才知道嘛
New information.
这肯定不行
That's stupid.
谁会花七块买我的蛋糕啊
No one would pay $7 for one of my cupcakes.
你确定吗 看这...
Really? 'Cause...
果然有遗传你爸弄钱的基因啊
Well, at least we know you're not adopted.
你怎么会沦落到来布鲁克林打工
So how'd you even end up in Brooklyn?
我去招工网站
Oh, I went on monster.com.
输入 上东区的人[富人区]
Typed in "place where nobody
这辈子绝对不会去的地方
from the Upper East Side would ever go, ever,"
就出现这家店了
and this diner came up.
这里治安差 穿高级皮衣
You can't wear a fancy leather jacket outside
铁定会被抢
in this neighborhood.
反着穿 露出丑的那面
You have to turn it inside out.
皮草 算了 再翻回来吧
Fur. Cool. Turn it back.
你住哪儿呀
So where do you live?
我家大宅被银行没收查封了
Our townhouse was taken and bolted up by the bank, so...
我需要表达一下同情吗
Is this where I'm supposed to feel sorry for you?
我是不想逼你啦
I mean, I don't want you to,
不过正常的好人都会同情的
but just so you know, a well-adjusted person would.
我是没同情心的坏人
I'm dead inside.
是人都看得出来
You make that pretty obvious.
好吧 我要去市中心的朋友家了
Anyway, I'm just gonna stay in the city with a friend.
我就住附近
I live a couple of blocks that way.
我照理该陪你走去地铁站的
I'd walk you to the subway,
不过我真的没这么好心
it's just that I don't want to.
完全理解
Got it.
就这样吧
Okay.
罗比
Robbie!
放这么大声干嘛呢
Why is the music so loud?
现在都凌晨三点了
It's 3:00 in the morning.
对不起嘛
I'm sorry.
原谅你吧 你们在干嘛呢
It's cool. So what are you doin'?
乐队在练习呢
The band's practicing.
怎么没看到乐器呢
But you're not playing any instruments.
这是我们独门秘技
Yeah, that's how we practice.
听着别人的音乐
We, like, listen to other good music,
然后在自己脑海演练
and play it in our head.
这好比不能弹的秘密
It's like the secret.
是吗 我也有个秘密要跟你们说
Well, I have a secret for you guys.
给我滚出去
Get out!
-伙计们先走吧 -好的
- Uh, you guys better go. - We should go.
抱歉了 我还得做小蛋糕呢
Sorry guys, I still have to make the cupcakes.
干嘛自己做 去店里买一个不就得了
Cupcakes? For why? You can just buy 'em at the store.
起来再做吧 宝贝 现在是滚床单时间
You can do that in the morning, babe, come to bed.
不行 我明早十点要到市中心
No, I can't. I have to be in the city by 10:00.
好吧 给你三分钟
Fine. You can have three minutes.
好吧 看在八块腹肌的份上 给你八分钟
Fine, you can have eight, one for each ab.
关门请注意
Stand clear of the closing doors.
太好了 死前心愿又完成了一样
Well, I can cross that off my bucket list.
我有电击棒
I have a taser!
天啊
Oh, my God.
真是万分抱歉
I am so sorry.
我以为这只是粉红小电棒
I didn't think it would hurt so much. It's pink.
我都要被电成炭粉了
It didn't feel pink.
我刚真不知道是你
I didn't know it was you.
我还以为自己被人强奸了呢
I thought I was being raped.
摸你的手算个屁强奸啊
That's not what rape feels like.
昨晚...你是在地铁上睡的吗
Did you... did you sleep on the subway?
我没地可去
I had nowhere else to go,
又不敢睡大街上
and I'm too afraid to sleep outside on the street.
天啊 还真是娇生惯养
God, you're spoiled.
下一站 格林中心
Next stop, Greenpoint.
快拿好你的行李
Ugh, get your stuff, come on!
我带你去我家吧 快点
I'll take you to my place, but hurry.
我要三十分钟内赶回市中心
Cause I have to be in the city in 30 minutes.
要打给我哦
Call me.
天啊 你家进贼啦
Oh, my god, you've been robbed!
我家本来就这样
This is how it always looks.
天啊 你家真不错
Oh, my God, totally cute!
好了 我四点回来
All right, I'll be back at 4:00,
然后我们一起上班
and we can go to work together.
卫生间 卧室
Bathroom, bedroom,
睡到四点才醒的男友 院子
boyfriend sleeps till 4:00, yard.
你还有个院子
Oh, you have a yard.
感觉是放松吸毒两相宜的好地方
Looks like a really nice place to relax and do crack.
那可不
It is.
我得走了 不然我打工要迟到了
I gotta go, I'm gonna be late for my other job in the city.
你打两份工吗
You have two jobs?
对 还给一个曼哈顿社交女王看孩子
Yes, I babysit for a Manhattan socialite diva.
现在又多了一个
Now I have a set.
抱歉来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
谢天谢地 你终于来了
Oh, thank God you're here,
宝宝身上有一股地下臭水沟的味儿
there is a bridge and tunnel smell over by the babies
快把我熏死了
that's stressing me out.
应该是要换尿布了
Their diapers probably need to be changed.
又要换啊 我肯定上午保姆才换了
Again? I swear, the morning nanny just did that.
当妈可真不容易
Motherhood is for reals.
麦克斯 我的推特密码是什么
Max, remind me, what's my Twitter password?
“推特密码”
Twitter password.
对啦
Yes!
嗨 布莱德 安洁莉娜
Hi, Brad. Hi, Angelina.
麦克斯 你也是家人 我有话想跟你说
Max, I need to tell you something because we're family.
先给我拿瓶常温的水
Now get me room temperature water and come over here.
我们是钱宁骗局的受害者
We are victims of the Channing Ponzi scheme.
我 大卫 还有布莱洁莉娜
Me, David, and Brangelina.
你们损失了多少
How much money did you lose?
握紧我的手
Hold my hands.
分毫未损
Nothing.
不过吓死人家了
But it really scared me.
帮我打开吧
Open that?
你认识卡洛琳·钱宁吗
So do you know Caroline Channing?
不认识 她什么都没有了
No, but she lost everything.
她一分钱都没有了
She has no money.
你能想像没钱的滋味吗
Can you imagine having no money?
我是指 穷的连钱都没有了
I mean, you wouldn't even have any money.
金句快发推特啊
You should twit that.
树倒猴孙散 墙倒众人推
And no one will even talk to her.
据说她为了找安身之地
I heard she went to six different friends' houses
去敲了六个朋友的家门
for a place to stay,
可他们都假装不在家
and they all had to pretend they weren't home.
-这太过分了 -对啊
- That's not cool. - Yeah.
-真是不幸 -对啊
- That's really sad. - So sad.
听的都心碎了
Breaks my heart.
当妈带孩子 人都多愁善感了
I guess motherhood has really opened me up emotionally.
麦克斯 我想抱抱我的宝宝
Max, I need to hold one of the babies,
帮我抱个过来
bring me one.
我要另一个 这个是次品
No, the other one. That's not the good one.
-你好 -你好
- Hello. - Oh, hi.
抱歉吵醒你了
Oh, I'm so sorry if I woke you up.
-你是谁啊 -麦克斯的朋友
- Who are you? - I'm Max's friend.
这话你可别跟她说
Uh, don't tell her I said that.
她要知道我自称是她的朋友
I have a feeling if she heard me call her my friend,
她会冲过来杀我
she'd stab me.
你在这干嘛呢
What are you doin' over there?
洗我的制服
Just washing my uniform,
让它变美美
trying to make it a little more cute
洗去那层污垢
and a little less crusty.
小心
Oh, watch out!
抱歉 我的错
Oh! Sorry, oh, my...
你有毛巾或抹布
Do you have a towel or a rag?
-之类的吗 -没关系 我来搞定
-Or something? - No, I... I got it.
好吧
Oh, okay.
在下罗比
I'm Robbie.
在下不舒服
I'm uncomfortable.
你害人家都湿了
You're getting me wet.
正有此意
That's the point.
你是麦克斯的男友
You're Max's boyfriend.
没关系的
It's cool.
不 有关系
No, it's not.
走开 卖肉男
Back up, Jersey shore.
你真可悲
You're pathetic,
而且还是被一个无家可归
and that's coming from someone who's homeless
无衣可换的人说
and wearing white after a labor day.
姐见过身材更好的
And I've seen better.
才怪 你骗人
No, you haven't.
你怎么没等我
Hey. Why didn't you wait for me?
不是说好一起过来的吗
I thought we were coming over together.
我想早点来把番茄酱"联姻"起
Oh. Um, I wanted to get here early to marry the ketchups.
今天我听说了你的惨况
Listen, I heard something really upsetting about you today.
他怎么说的 说我投怀送抱吗
What did he say, that I came on to him?
"他"是指...
Him who?
没啥
Nothing.
你是说罗比 对吧
Him, Robbie?
这事与我无关
It's none of my business,
但我觉得那家伙跟你配不上
but you deserve better than that guy.
对 这事的确与你无关
Yeah, it is none of your business.
唉 我刚刚对你起了一丝怜悯之情
Ooh, I was just starting to feel sorry for you.
我是说 你可以找个更好的
I'm just saying, you're worth more than that.
是吗 我该相信你的话吗
What, I'm supposed to believe you about this?
你连简历都作假
The person who lied on their resume,
还用蛋糕赚差价 你就是个大骗子
and lied about the cupcakes... you're a liar.
-我是想帮你啊 -那好吧
- I'm just trying to help. - You know what?
既然你什么都懂
Since you seem to know so much about everything,
干嘛不带着你的沃顿学位
why don't you take your wharton degree,
跟可笑的外套 找一个能收留你的地方
and your ridiculous coat, and figure this all out yourself.
-麦克斯 等等 -瞧
- Max.Max, wait. - Oh, look,
对街的拱廊之火乐队演唱会刚结束
The Arcade Fire concert just let out across the street,
祝你好运
good luck with that.
她会回来的吧
She's coming back, right?
这满屋子的顾客
She's not gonna leave me here alone
她不会丢下我一个人的 对吧
with a restaurant full of people?
我就这么跟你说吧
Let me put it to you this way.
你就跟晚上在施瓦辛格家
You might as well be a night maid
落单的女佣一样
at the Schwarzenegger house.
要被狠操一顿了
You got screwed.
-爽 -太爽了
- Oh. - Oh, yeah.
爽死我了
That feels so good.
把铃鼓换来这个位置
Now put your tambourine around it.
亲爱的 我回来了
Hi, honey, I'm home.
在我下班前滚蛋
I want you gone by the time I get back.
宝贝宝贝 听我解释
Babe! Babe, I can explain.
你回家太早了嘛
You weren't supposed to be home.
人家说你配不上我
People say I deserve better than you.
谁 那个金发妞吗
Who? That blonde girl?
她懂个屁 就会瞎说
She doesn't know what she's talkin' about.
人家是沃顿毕业的
She went to Wharton
还去过瑞士呢
and Switzerland.
快看快看
Yo, yo. Look at that.
那妞儿干起活来比史蒂芬·霍金
That girl is workin' harder than Stephen Hawking
扣袖口还努力呢
tryin' to put in a pair of cufflinks.
来 我来帮你
Here, let me help you with that.
我不要人帮
I don't need any help.
每个人都有需要帮忙的时候
Everyone needs help sometimes.
你们上错菜了
This isn't what I ordered.
她叫卡洛琳
This is Caroline.
她可能会下错单
She may have gotten your order wrong,
但她起码有些事情没做错
but she does get some things right.
谢谢
Thank you.
不 是我要谢谢你
No, thank you.
你到底看上那家伙哪点
What'd you see in that guy, anyway?
他这里的肌肉不错
He had these muscle thingies.
-那里呀 -是啊
- Oh,those things? - Yeah.
我不知道那里怎么叫
I don't know what those are called,
但是好女孩看了就会意乱情迷
but they make smart girls stupid.
麦克斯
Max!
还以为今晚见不到你的小翘臀呢
I thought your tight ass wasn't coming in tonight,
我的心都快碎了
and my heart broke in half.
奥列格
You know what, Oleg?
这话我爱听
I needed that.
如果
So I...
你要找地方住的话 咱俩可以当室友
I need a roommate, if you wanna crash.
真不是我说 地铁都比你家干净
Not gonna lie, the subway's cleaner than your couch.
我好像对你有些好感了
I just felt myself starting to like you.
真的吗 我真觉得我们可...
Really? Because I really feel like we could...
我就知道纯属错觉
I knew that wouldn't last.
走吧
Come on.
明天我们去市里
Tomorrow we can go into the city
把你剩下的东西搬回来
and get the rest of your stuff.
全部都锁起来了
Everything's locked up.
没有一样你喜欢的东西是可以拿回来的吗
What, you have nothing that you care about that we can get?
好像还真有一样
Well, there is one thing.
居然没人拦我们 真是奇了怪了
The weirdest thing is that nobody stopped us.
把它养在这里
I'm gonna save a fortune,
比养在马厩里省钱多了
keeping him here instead of in the stables.
什么时候想到这养马大计的
When did you put this whole horse-in-my-yard thing together?
这就是我
I can't help it.
只要有机可乘 我绝不让它溜走
I see an opportunity, and I make it happen,
比如你的纸杯蛋糕
like with your cupcakes.
关我的小蛋糕啥事
Like what with my cupcakes?
听好了 开一家蛋糕店
Ready? To open a bake shop,
只需要二十五万启动资金来
all we need is 250 grand start-up money,
租店面 和买一些基本设备
for the real estate, and the basic equipment...
是嘛
Yeah. Oh.
-二十五万就够了吗 -对
- 250 grand,that's all? - Yeah.
我去星巴克的时候
Did freakin' Chestnut here kick you in the head
你的脑子让栗宝给踢了吗
while I was in Starbucks?
听我说完
Hear me out.
要是我们两人同时打两份工
If we both worked two jobs
一周进账两千块
and made $2,000 a week,
我们就可以在一年后开蛋糕店了
we could open a cupcake business in a little over a year.
过去两天我们赚了三百八十七块
In the past two days, we've made $387,
这是个不错的开始
and that's a good start.
我们还能兼职别的工作赚外快呀
We can make extra money at other jobs,
比如做公关 广告行政
like publicists, advertising executives...
看门 运毒
janitors, drug mules.
看来得先提升你的自尊
We really need to work on your self-esteem.
所以说
So...
你的美味小蛋糕 加上我的商科背景
You, cupcakes, me, business background,
我们就等于成功 怎样
us, success. What do you think?
你还有匹马
I think you have a horse.
是我们有匹马
I think we have a horse.
不要爱上我
Don't get attached.